export const questions = [
  {
    question: "Identify the sharps in G",
    answer: ["Gb/F#"],
  },
  {
    question: "Identify the sharps in D",
    answer: ["Gb/F#", "Db/C#"],
  },
  {
    question: "Identify the sharps in A",
    answer: ["Gb/F#", "Db/C#", "Ab"],
  },
  {
    question: "Identify the sharps in E",
    answer: ["Gb/F#", "Db/C#", "Ab", "Eb"],
  },
  {
    question: "Identify the sharps in B",
    answer: ["Gb/F#", "Db/C#", "Ab", "Eb", "Bb"],
  },
  {
    question: "Identify the flats in Gb/F#",
    answer: ["Gb/F#", "Db/C#", "Ab", "Eb", "Bb", "B"],
  },
  {
    question: "Identify the flats in Db/C#",
    answer: ["Gb/F#", "Db/C#", "Ab", "Eb", "Bb"],
  },
  {
    question: "Identify the flats in Ab",
    answer: ["Db/C#", "Ab", "Eb", "Bb"],
  },
  {
    question: "Identify the flats in Eb",
    answer: ["Ab", "Eb", "Bb"],
  },
  {
    question: "Identify the flats in Bb",
    answer: ["Eb", "Bb"],
  },
  {
    question: "Identify the flats in F",
    answer: ["Bb"],
  },
];
